Jayla Newton

SKILLS

JavaScript
HTML
Materialize
CSS
API Design Knowledge
jQuery
mySQL
Sequelize
MongoDB
Node
Express

EXPERIENCE

H-E-B, Pflugerville, TX - Cashier

Feb 2019 - Jul 2020

- Helped check customers out in a quick and orderly fashion.
- Assisted customers with any issues they were having.

Trellis Company, Round Rock, TX - CSR

Jul 2020 - Aug 2021

- Took inbound calls and assisted claimants set up their claim.
- Assisted claimants with any issues they were having.
- Took 100-200 calls on a daily basis.

EDUCATION

University of Texas, Austin, TX - Full Stack Coding Bootcamp

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021, Austin, TX

Professional Summary

Full Stack Web Developer in the MERN stack, specializing in JavaScript and Node. Expertise in developing web pages using HTML5, CSS3, MVC, SASS, Object Oriented JavaScript, ES6, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, XML, REACT. Good understanding of Document Object Model (DOM) and DOM functions. Extensive use of Node environment using NPM, Express, mySQL and MongoDB along with Mongoose.JS to create server side applications. Experience in creating the user validation forms and using the RESTful services for sending the data to the server. Great experience on working with CSS Background, padding, table, Animations, Pseudo classes and Layouts, positioning, border, margin, Pseudo elements and CSS behaviors including the Box Model and Flex properties.